Lost for centuries... only one man can activate it!
The Guyver is a science fiction, action film directed by Steve Wang.
FBI agent Max Reed witnesses Dr.
Tetsu Segawa - a researcher for the mysterious
Chronos Corporation - being murdered.
Segawa had stolen an alien device known as "The Guyver" from Chronos.
College student Sean Barker, whose girlfriend's father was Dr.
Segawa, finds the Guyver's hiding spot while watching the
forensic team investigating the crime scene.
Sean Barker / The Guyver, played by Jack Armstrong.
Max Reed, played by Mark Hamill.
Mizky Segawa, played by Vivian Wu.
Dr. Tetsu Segawa, played by Greg Joung Paik.
Striker, played by Jimmie Walker.
Ramsey, played by Peter Spellos.
The Guyver (released in Europe and South America as Mutronics) is a 1991 science fiction tokusatsu
superhero film directed by Screaming Mad George and Steve Wang, and produced by Brian Yuzna.
Loosely based on the Japanese manga series of the same name by Yoshiki Takaya, the film was produced in conjunction with
Shochiku Films; the film stars Mark Hamill, Vivian Wu, Jack Armstrong, Jimmie Walker, and David Gale.
The Guyver follows a young man, Sean Barker (Jack Armstrong), who discovers an alien artifact called
"The Unit" which transforms him into an alien-hybrid super soldier called "The Guyver".
Barker learns that a major corporation known as Chronos is after the Guyver unit, and
soon discovers that the company seeks to genetically engineer monsters.
The film was met with a mixed reaction from critics and fans.
A sequel followed in 1994 called Guyver: Dark Hero.
The film explores themes of superhero, based on manga, guyver.
The tone is thought_provoking.